Attention To:

Human Resources Department

Dear Sir/Madam,

I found that your company is looking for employee. And I believe it is fit with my background

education or my experience.

My name is Rayi Pertiwi, I am twenty five years old. I graduated from Citra Mandiri High School

of Office Administration in May 2014 and until now I am still studying Guidance and Counseling

at Indraprastha University. I consider myself that I have qualifications as you want. I active,

skillful, creative, problem solver and multi skill individual seeking a position that offers both

challege and a good opportunity industrial growth. More than 4 years of experience working at

Lazada Group as Analyst, Vendor Relationship Management and a little internship experience at

Soho Group.

With my qualifications, I confident that I will be able to contribute effectively to your company.

Herewith I enclose my:

1. Pas color photograph 4x6 cm

2. Copy of Letter (KTP)

3. Curriculum Vitae

4. Certificate of Health

5. Letter of Work Experience

6. Transcript Value Semester 1 and 2 (Bachelor)

7. Copy of High School Certificate

8. Copy of Transcript Value one sheet (Senior High School)

9. Copy of Police Notes (SKCK)

10. Copy of Certificate of Competency

11. Copy of Internship Certificate

I would express my gratitude for your attention and I hope I could be the part of your company.

Sincerely,

Rayi Pertiwi

HP: 0813-8507-0732



JAKARTA TIMUR

NIK : 3175066411950002

Marso. RAYLPERTIWE

Tempat/Tol Lahir : CIMANGGU, 24-11-1985

Jenes Automin : PEREMPUAN Gol. Darah : O : KP. JEMBATAN

Atamat

RT/RW 1010/00/2

KeyDesa PENGGILINGAN

Kecamatan -CLAKLINES:

ISLAM Acaamo

Status Perkawinan, BELUM KAWIN

Pokeriage : KARYAWAN SWASTA

Kewarganegaraan: WNI

Berlaka Hingga : SEUMUR HIDUR



JAKABTA TIMUB 24-01-2016



RAYI PERTIWI

DETAILS

Contacts

Kp. Jembatan RT. 011 / 012 No. 98, Penggilingan, Cakung, East Jakarta, 13940, Indonesia rayi.pertiwi.rp@gmail.com 081385070732

Date / Place of birth

November 24, 1995 Cimanggu

Nationality

Indonesian

PROFILE

Analyst, Vendor Relationship Management with more than 4 years working experience. Creative problem solver with strong interpersonal skills. Managed to become the "Best Report RTM (Return to Merchant) 2016 from all of Lazada Asia" and resolve ticket complaints 90% every day. I am good at using Microsoft Office (Word, Excel and Power Point), I am used to using Zendesk and Salesforce and I also know the process administration because of my educational background.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Analyst, Vendor Relationship Management, PT. Lastana Express Indonesia / LAZADA GROUP, Depok

- Contact the customer to ensure the package has been received properly
- Handling customer and seller complaints
- Processing data, updating status, monitoring and making reports for items returned to the seller
- Processing data, updating status, monitoring and making reports for goods sent to customers from retail, fbl, crossborder and marketplace
- Processing data, updating status, monitoring and making reports for items returned by the customer to the lazada
- Maintaining good relations between customers with lazada, lazada with shipping services
- Achievement : Best Report RTM (Return to Merchant) 2016 from all of Lazada Asia

Sales Promotion Girl, PT. AWS FOODS, East Jakarta

MAY 2015 - JULY 2015

- Achieve maximum work productivity
- Achieve Target Sales
- Maintain Shrinkage Rate (lost item number)

- Give correct information to customers
- Maintain the cleanliness of Sales and Merchandise Areas

Crew Store, PT. Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk, East Jakarta

JUNE 2014 - JULY 2014

- Serve all types of payments
- Offering products that are being promoted
- Check incoming money (prevent counterfeit money from entering the safe)
- Prevents a minus or difference in money at the end of the shift (the number of items sold must match the money coming in during the shift)

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Indraprasta University, East Jakarta

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT

I am an active student in semester 3 majoring in guidance and counseling. I am still in college every Friday (8.00 p.m - 10.00 p.m) and Saturday (7.00 a.m - 3.00 p.m).

Citra Mandiri Senior High School, East Jakarta

MAY 2011 - MAY 2014

- First rank since class 1 semester 1 to class 3 semester 6
- The 4th highest score in the National Examination in Citra Mandiri High School

LINKS

Linked Instagram

SKILLS

Microsoft Office	Movie Maker
Data Management	Communication and Presentation

INTERNSHIPS

Internship in Fixed Asset Spare Part Procurement Dept, PT. Soho Industri Pharmasi / SOHO GROUP, East Jakarta

JANUARY 2013 - APRIL 2013

- Receive an incoming call and forward it back to the person concerned
- Sort incoming and outgoing mail
- Receive exchange of purchase orders from the vendor
- Arrange purchase orders based on manufacturing date
- Compare the prices of goods from catalogs sent by vendors
- Create a meeting schedule and reserve a meeting room

LANGUAGES

Indonesian English

HOBBIES

- +Read books, articles and novels
- +Writing a story or poetry
- +Design
- +Arrange the layout of items in a room
- +Making handicrafts



" KLINIK PENGGILINGAN"

JI. Raya Penggilingan No. 16 Jakarta Timur Telp. (021) 4610131
PENANGGUNG JAWAB

Dr. ALIMAT

SIP: 2.101.3172.0109/5.60.03.04.071 PRAKTEK DOKTER 24 JAM





SURAT KETERANGAN BERBADAN SEHAT

Yang be	rtanda tangan dibawal	h ini menerangkai	n bahwa setelah r	nemeriksa :
Nama	Paux Pertin	í		
Umur	25th			
Alamat	Ky Jembstan	Rt 11/12 m	98 Jungert	magan
	Ky Jembelan Columa (Johnson J.	nuy	0
	emeriksaan yang dilak			
sehat.				
	eterangan ini diberikan Luman ke (g			
	V	Jaka	erta 25	20.20
BB TB TD	:46kg : 54cm			10
10	: 110/mm/Hg	(d	Dr. PRAYITI	0.03.54.071
			/1	



PT. INDOPSIKO INDONESIA

EXCELLENCE SKILL AND STRONG LEADERSHIP CONSULTANT PSYCHOLOGICAL EMPLOYEE

JL. PAHLAWAN REVOLUSI NO. 59 JAKARTA TIMUR TELP. 8615604 FAX. 8611507 (DEPAN BCA)

CERTIFICATE OF EMPLOYMENT SURAT KETERANGAN KERJA

No.126/HRD/V/17

This is to certify that Dengan ini menerangkan bahwa

Name Nama : RAYI PERTIWI

Date of Birth

Tempat Tanggal Lahir

: CIMANGGU, 24 NOVEMBER 1995

Point of Assignment

: PT. LASTANA EXPRESS INDONESIA

Position / Dept

Jabatan

: VENDOR RELATION 3 PL

Service Period

Masa Kerja

: From 23 November 2015 Up To 30 September 2016

Dari - Sampai Dengan :

Reason for Leaving
Alasan Berhenti

: The expiration of the Employment Agreement

Berakhirnya Masa Perjanjian Kerja

We would like to take this opportunity to thank you for you past effort and contribution to PT INDOPSIKO INDONESIA. We wish you every success in the future, Kami mengucapkan terimakasih atas usaha dan dedikasi yang di berikan kepada PT INDOPSIKO INDONESIA, semoga prestasi dan keberhasilan senantiasa menyertai saudara di waktu yang akan datang.

Jakarta, 24 MEI 2017 PT. INDOPSIKO INDONESIA

RUSTINI, SE Hrd. Manager





GD. Capital Place LT. 20 Jl. Jend. Gatot Subroto Kav. 18, Kuningan Barat Mampang Prapatan, Jakarta Selatan Indonesia 12710 Telp. 021 80630210

Jakarta, 30 July 2020

To Whom It May Concern

This is to certify that **Ms. Rayi Pertiwi** has been employed at PT. LASTANA EXPRESS INDONESIA since 1 October 2016 to 31 July 2020. Her last position is Analyst, Vendor Relationship Management in Lazada eLogistics-Indonesia-Transport-Local team Department.

Yours faithfully, PT. LASTANA EXPRESS INDONESIA



Jane Evelyn Tansy

Vice President, Compensation & Benefits

Transkrip Nilai

Semester: 1 Tahun Ajar: Gasal 2019/2020

No	Kode Matkul	Nama Mata Kuliah	Kelas	SKS	Nilai Huruf	Nilai Angka	SKS x NA
1	KB01G120	Dasar-Dasar Pelayanan BK *)	XD	3	A-	3.75	11.25
2	KK01G110	Dasar-Dasar Ilmu Pendidikan *)	XD	3	B+	3.25	9.75
3	KK01G111	Psikologi Umum *)	XD	3	A-	3.75	11.25
4	PK01G101	Agama	XD	2	A-	3.75	7.50
5	KK01G104	Komputer Dasar #)	YD	2	A	4.00	8.00
6	PB01G130	Psikologi Konseling	YD	2	В	3.00	6.00
7	PK01G102	Pancasila	YD	2	A-	3.75	7.50
8	PK01G107	Bahasa Indonesia	YD	2	B-	2.75	5.50
			Jumlah	19		28.00	66.75
		Indeks Prestasi Se	emester (IPS)	3.51			

Semester: 2 Tahun Ajar: Genap 2019/2020

No	Kode Matkul	Nama Mata Kuliah Kela	as	SKS	Nilai Huruf	Nilai Angka	SKS x NA
1	KK01G213	Psikologi Perkembangan Anak & Remaja *)		3	А	4.00	12.00
2	PB01G233	Psikologi Sosial *)		2	A-	3.75	7.50
3	PB01G243	Pengembangan Profesi Konseling *)		3	A-	3.75	11.25
4	PB01G256	Manajemen BK		3	А	4.00	12.00
5	KB01G231	Psikologi Pendidikan		2	B+	3.25	6.50
6	KK01G203	Kewarganegaraan		2	A-	3.75	7.50
7	KK01G212	Belajar dan Pembelajaran		2	В	3.00	6.00
8	KK01G223	Filsafat Ilmu		2	A-	3.75	7.50
		J	umlah	19		29.25	70.25
		Indeks Prestasi Semester	r (IPS)	3,70			

. . . .







SURAT KETERANGAN HASIL UJIAN NASIONAL

SEKOLAH MENENGAH KEJURUAN PROGRAM 3 TAHUN

TAHUN PELAJARAN 2013/2014

Program Studi Keahlian : ...Administrasi

Kompetensi Keahlian : Administrasi Perkantoran

Yang bertanda tangan di bawah ini, Kepala Sekolah Menengah Kejuruan

CITRA MANDIRI, Kota Administrasi Jakarta Timur menerangkan bahwa:

nama : RAYI PERTIWI

tempat dan tanggal lahir : .CILACAP. 24 NOVEMBER 1995

sekolah asal : .SMK.CITRA.MANDIRI......

nomor peserta ujian nasional : .4-14-01-05-193-075-6.....

LULUS/TIDAK LULUST

Ujian Nasional berdasarkan Peraturan Menteri Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan Nomor 97 Tahun 2013 dengan hasil sebagai berikut:

No.	Mata Pelajaran	Nilai Sekolah	Nilai Ujian Nasional	Nilai Akhir ²⁾
1	Bahasa Indonesia	8,99	7,80	8,3
2	Bahasa Inggris	8,79	6,40	7,4
3 Matematika		9,01	7,25	8,0
4	Kompetensi Keahlian	9,07	8,91	9,0
	Jumlah	35,86	30,36	32,7

¹ Coret yang tidak perlu

Nilai Akhir = 40% Nilai Sekolah + 60% Nilai Ujian Nasional



DN-01 Mk 0063650



SURAT KETERANGAN CATATAN KEPOLISIAN POLICE RECORD

Nomor: SKCK/YANMAS/04179/VIII/YAN,2,3/2020/RES,JAKTIM

Diterangkan bersama ini

This is to certify that : Nama

Name Jenis Kelamin

Sex Kebangsaan Nationality

Agama Religion

Tempat dan Tanggal lahir

Tempat tinggal sekarang Current Address

Place and date of birth

: CIMANGGU, 24 November 1995 KP, JEMBATAN NO. 39 RT 10 RW 02 PENGGILINGAN CAKUNG KOTA

JAKARTA TIMUR

: RAYI PERTIWI

: PEREMPUAN

: INDONESIA

: ISLAM

Pekeriaan Occupation

: MAHASISWA Nomor Kartu Tanda Penduduk : 3175066411950002

Citizen card Number

Nomor Passport/KITAS/KITAP

Passport/KITAS/KITAP

Rumus Sidik Jari Fingerprints Formula 4 I 1 U 100 13

L 18 R 101

Setelah diadakan penelitian hingga saat dikeluarkan surat ini yang didasarkan kepada : As of screening through the Issue here of by virtue of :

Catatan Kepolisian yang ada

Existing Police Record

bahwa nama tersebut diatas tidak memiliki catatan atau keterlibatan dalam kegiatan kriminal apapun the bearer hereof proves not to be involved in any criminal cases

selama ia berada di Indonesia during his/her stay in Indonesia : 24 November 1995

sampai dengan

: 19 Agustus 2020

Keterangan ini diberikan berhubungan dengan permohonan This certificate is issued at the request to the application

Untuk keperluan/menuju* For the Purpose or to

MELAMAR PEKERJAAN

Berlaku dari tanggal

19 Agustus 2020

Valid from Sampai dengan

Until

: 19 Februari 2021

Dikeluarkan di : Jakarta Issued in

Pada Tanggal : 19 Agustus 2020

KEPOLISIAN RESORT METRO JAKTIM KASAT INTELKAM

Apabla dikemudian hari ybs terfibat kejahatan/pelanggaran.

PT. MATAHARI DEPARTMENT STORE Tbk





SERTIFIKAT UJI KOMPETENSI

CERTIFICATE OF COMPETENCY

Nomor: I4I/SMK-CM/UKK/V/2014

No.: 01.05.F6045.075.6

Sertifikat diselenggarakan berdasarkan Peraturan Menteri Pendidikan Nomor 97 Tahun 2013 tentang Ujian Nasional Tahun Pelajaran 2013/2014 dan Keputusan Badan Standar Nasional Pendidikan (BSNP) Nomor 0022/P/BSNP/I/2013 tentang Petunjuk Operasional Sekolah (POS) Ujian Nasional SMK Tahun Pelajaran 2013/2014

Menyatakan bahwa:

RAYI PERTIWI

Lahir di

: Cilacap, 24 November 1995

Sekolah Asal

: SMK CITRA MANDIRI JAKARTA

Dinyatakan LULUS Ujian Praktik Kejuruan dan diakui telah memiliki Kompetensi seperti tercantum dibalik sertifikat ini.

Kepala SMK Citra Mandiri

SMK

AR-RAHMAH

CITRA MANDIRI

Drs. H. Ajuddin HS



Jakarta, 20 Mei 2014 PT. Matahari Department Store Tbk

Purwaningsin, S. Sos

Manager



SOHO GROUP

Sertifikat

Diberikan kepada:

Rayi Pertiwi

Telah melaksanakan Praktek Kerja Lapangan di Fixed Asset & Spare Part Procrument Dept.

Periode: 30 Januari 2013 - 26 April 2013

Jakarta, 23 September 2013

Marios

Maria Jenny

Recruitment & Training Support Sect. Head

SOHO Group

Yuvianty Soesilowati

Recruitment & Performance Management Dept. Head